Accessing the REST API

The REST API for our backend is hosted on Heroku at 'https://backr.herokuapp.com/'. Previously, we used test.js to access our endpoints locally, but we've moved on to bigger and better things! 
Our frontend will communicate with our backend using the endpoints we've implemented in our /routes directory. This data that's passed from the backend to the the asynchronous 'fetch' call in our react-native code will be used to populate our back.r

Files:
back.r/routes (Server)
- Contains endpoints. Hosted on Heroku
back.r/react_app/screens (Client)
- Frontend files

Take a look at 

