Connecting the database to the endpoints

- In database.js we export the function 'connect' with module.exports.connect. This allows other files to use the connect() function, as long as they import the database.js file using 'var db = require('./database.js');'. It also contains the addUser function which we will be calling later.

- In server.js, we create an instance of the database, which is shared between all files so that we don't need to keep opening the database each time we get or post data to it. We require database.js in order to call the connect() function

- In user.js, we post to the database using the url '/addNew' using the global variable db which we created earlier. This makes a call to database.js's function 'addUser' which adds user information to the "User" database.

1. Navigate to the Back.r directory
2. Start the server with 'npm start'
- You should see:
	App now running on port 8080
	connected to database
Note the lag in between when the app is running and when we are connected to the database. We shouldn't make a call 
3. Open another terminal window
4. Enter curl command to call '/addNew': 'curl -X POST http://localhost:8080/user/addNew'
- You should see this message in the terminal window you started your server in: 
	'inserted NAME into database'
5. NAME is now in the User database. Try changing NAME in user.js to add other names!