Accessing the REST API

The REST API for our backend is hosted on Heroku at 'https://backr.herokuapp.com/'. Previously, we used test.js to access our endpoints locally, but we've moved on to bigger and better things! 
Our frontend will communicate with our backend using the endpoints we've implemented in our /routes directory. This data that's passed from the backend to the the asynchronous 'fetch' call in our react-native code will be used to populate our back.r

Files:
back.r/routes (Server)
- Contains endpoints. Hosted on Heroku
back.r/react_app/screens (Client)
- Frontend files

Example in MatchesScreen

Take a look at MatchesScreen.js in the react_app. We define a function 'getChannels' (ln 13) which makes a call to an endpoint in twilio.js. It uses the react-native function 'fetch' to make a GET HTTP request to our API and returns the response in a promise after the channels are fetched.

const getChannels = function() {
  return fetch( url + 'twilio/channels?identity=vylana&endpointId=9998', {
    method: 'GET',
    headers: {
    'Accept': 'application/json',
    'Content-Type': 'application/json',
    }
  }).then(function(response) {
    return response.json()
  })
}

We can refer to routes/twilio.js to get the appropriate url and required body (only in POST requests). For the request, we'll refer to '/channels' (ln 29). There's no need to change anything in this file, but it's good to use as reference and to get an idea of what's going to be returned to you. We see that the response object is defined around line 45. This is the object you can expect to receive in a successful call to the API.


This response is returned to the call to getChannels() (ln 114) which assigns the appropriate object within the response to this.state.users (created on ln 107). This allows the object to be updated after it is initialized.

In render() we see that this.state.users is called in order to display on the matches screen. This is reflected onto the screen :)

